I'm going to tell you guys a story about
my grandma uh this is very true I went
back home and I visited my grandma my
grandmother helped raise me she one my
favorite people in the world uh when
I've been back home I guess in the two
years since I had gone back home uh she
had come down with a pretty bad case of
dementia and when I mentioned it to my
dad who had been dealing with for two
years he's like yeah I I don't know what
happened it's like we took her to
Florida and she came back with
Alzheimer's well okay well I don't think
that's how it works um but here's my
point
if you have a grandma maybe keep her out
of Florida for a few
years just to be on the safe side right
who to say uh but it's bad cuz she's my
grandma and I love her you know and
she's getting she got to the point where
She's forgetting people's names she'll
lose her purse and her wallet and her
keys uh we left her alone for no more
than an hour and she became incontinent
had an accident and when we brought it
up with her she was really rude she was
like nah n that wasn't me now that must
have been somebody
else well
okay I don't know what the weirder
reality to believe is then right like on
the one hand my grandmother has gotten
up an age uh she's got a bad case of
dementia but that she has a family that
is more than willing and more than able
to love her and take care of her or
someone's breaking into my grandmother's
home pooping everywhere
pooping in her pants to frame her for
it and Leaving Without a
Trace I'm just like hey Grandma what
enemies did you make in your
youth that they are messing with you so
specifically and
weirdly what did you do as a
child my bigger point is that is an
ocean 11 movie I would watch
right they're in the warehouse they're
like let's go over the plan one more
time step one break into to Barbara's
house step two poop
everywhere and I mean everywhere
including her own pants we don't want
them asking
questions step three and this is really
important Tony look at me this is
important step three Steve feel
nothing the new guys in the back boss I
have a
question
why why are we doing this why do we keep
doing
this he just looks straight at the
camera camera Zooms in he goes Barbara
knows
why h